#Descripe progress
This project is processing signal PPG and PCG by C language on the PC. After that i will embedded this 
code into ESP32 to calculate the heart rate, blood pressure. 
Before i implement this project i processing PPG and PCG signal by Python language. So i have algorthim
to processing signal.
## The goal after this project done
i wil write code C to calculate SPO2 and display the heart rate, blood pressure, SPO2 on TFT display. 

